sydkaka@icloud.com https://www.linkedin.com/in/sunmr2

# SUMMARY

Hi everyone, I'm an experienced ServiceNow Developer with 3+ year experience. I have been working on Azure Cloud Integration, catalog item, workflow, flow designer and currently working with ITSM module as an Integration SME. I also have knowledge in Azure, Ansible automation, Azure DevOps, Agile and Linux. I have a passion with IT and IIOT. Thanks!

# **EXPERIENCE**

#### Application Engineer/ ServiceNow Developer ITSM

Chevron November 2020 - Present

Cloud Engineer/ ServiceNow

Developer

February 2019 - November Chevron

2020

Technical Analyst

Intern

Chevron May 2018 - August 2018

Software Engineering Internship

AJA Video Systems May 2017 - August 2017

Did Q&A test on problem video convertors and fixed issue on pixel shifting on V2 Digital convertor. Developing a utility tool for NTV2 SDK, parsing through Video cards' verilog code find input and output widget and check the router between them. Learning about video and audio standards.

Front Desk

August 2016 - January 2017 Rapid Graphics

assist costumers, providing excellent service

#### **EDUCATION**

Master's degree, Computer Software Engineering

2014 - 2018

Bachelor's degree , Computer Science

# **SKILLS**

C++

C

Oracle Database

IT Service Management

Object-Oriented Programming (OOP)

**Computer Security** 

HTML

CSS

С

Microsoft Azure

**Customer Service** 

ServiceNow

Web Application Security

Agile Application Development

**JavaScript** 

Microsoft Visual Studio Code

linuxs

ansible

**LANGUAGES** 

English

**LANGUAGES** 

Chinese (Simplified)

# **RECOMMENDATIONS**

He is very passionate about learning technologies and I am his Senior in the same group. He put all his efforts to learn ServiceNow Platform and within short span working with strong confidence and even troubleshooting the issues amazingly. He has very Good knowledge on ITSM, Core Configurations on Servicenow Platform, Cloud Management Platform.

--

# **CONTACT DETAILS**

Phone No.:

(Personal Number)

Email: sydkaka@icloud.com

Address: Walnut Creek, California, United States